<resources>
  <string name="application_name">Telescope Sample</string>
  <string name="launcher_name">Telescope</string>

  <string name="tab_default">Default</string>
  <string name="tab_device_info">Device Info</string>
  <string name="tab_styled">Styled</string>
  <string name="tab_children_only">Children Only</string>
  <string name="tab_three_finger">Three Finger</string>
  <string name="tab_other_target">Other Target</string>
  <string name="tab_additional_attachment">Additional Attachment</string>
  <string name="tab_maps">Maps</string>

  <string name="additional_attachment_description">
    The provided email launcher can be configured to attach another file. In this example, we
    attach a text file with some Shakespeare in it because we\'re classy like that.
  </string>
  <string name="default_description">
    Long press with two fingers to capture a bug report. An email will be pre-populated with an
    address and a subject. A screenshot will also be taken and automatically attached to the email
    for you.
  </string>
  <string name="device_info_description">
    The provided email launcher can be configured to populate the body of the email as well. In this
    example, the body is filled with the app version and information about the current device.
  </string>
  <string name="styled_description">
    The color of the bars are easily configured to match your theme.
  </string>
  <string name="children_only_description">
    By default, Telescope takes a screenshot of the entire window it is in. If you prefer, Telescope
    can be easily configured to only take a screenshot of the children inside the TelescopeLayout.
  </string>
  <string name="three_finger_description">
    Some of your views may already use two-finger gestures. Telescope can be configured to require
    any number of fingers to trigger. In this example, a three-finger press is required.
  </string>
  <string name="other_target_description">
    Telescope can be configured to take a screenshot of a different view. In this example, long
    press this container to take a screenshot of the view below.
  </string>
  <string name="maps_three_finger_description">
    Google Maps use two-finger gestures for pan and zooming. Three-finger press is required for this
    example.
  </string>

  <string name="attributions"><![CDATA[
    <b>
      Tap-And-Hold Icons
      (<a href="http://www.thenounproject.com/term/tap-and-hold/13944/">1</a>,
      <a href="http://www.thenounproject.com/term/tap-and-hold/13957/">2</a>)
    </b><br />
    <i>
      by <a href="http://www.thenounproject.com/Glimy">Gary Lim</a> from
      <a href="http://thenounproject.com">The Noun Project</a>
    </i>
  ]]></string>
</resources>
